<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Visible Raid Points</name>
	<author>1trickPwnyta</author>
	<packageId>visibleraidpoints.1trickPwnyta</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
Ever wondered just how many points the game used to generate a raid? Are you getting the maximum 10,000 point raids yet? Now you'll know because you can see exactly how many raid points are used to generate every raid and many other types of incidents.

For an even more educational experience, you can also enable a threat points breakdown that shows the details of how the points were calculated, line by line. This option must be turned on in the mod settings first and will not work and/or make sense with mods that alter the way threat points are calculated.

Spanish translation by Ferchu.
Korean translation by PenguinsCanFly.

Note: The current version of this mod is no longer compatible with version 1.2 of the game. For a 1.2-compatible version of the mod with reduced functionality, you can download it from the "1.2-compatibility" branch on GitHub: https://github.com/1trickPonyta/VisibleRaidPoints/tree/1.2-compatibility

Note: The threat points breakdown feature of this mod is not compatibile with my other mod, Unlimited Threat Scale (https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2562732435). For a compatibile version of the mod, you can download it from the "uts-compatibility" branch on GitHub: https://github.com/1trickPwnyta/VisibleRaidPoints/tree/uts-compatibility You will also need to download the compatible version of Unlimited Threat Scale at https://github.com/1trickPwnyta/UnlimitedThreatScale/tree/vrp-compatibility

=== Updates ===
10/26/2022: Updated to 1.4
03/09/2022: Created alternate version of the mod for compatibility with Unlimited Threat Scale
09/28/2021: Added extra error logging.
08/26/2021: Added threat points breakdown feature.
08/09/2021: Added Korean translation.
08/06/2021: Enabled visible threat points for additional incident types including infestations, crashed ship parts, mechanoid clusters, manhunter packs, animal mass insanity, and caravan ambushes. Added Spanish translation.

+++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++
If you enjoy my work and want to support me and my family, I take donations at:
https://ko-fi.com/1trickpwnyta
+++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++
</description>
	<url>https://github.com/1trickPonyta/VisibleRaidPoints</url>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
</ModMetaData>
